rfactorcentral.com 2016-04-07

# rFactor Central // Privacy Policy

###### Privacy Policy

Upon submitting any information and/or content of any form to this Site, You hereby agree to this Privacy Policy. This Agreement, heretofore referred to as the “Privacy Policy,” is entered into by and between Ignite Skill Gaming, Incorporated (“Ignite”) and You (“User”). 

Ignite collects, either directly, or through User’s providing information to rFactorcentral.com (the “Site”) User-submitted information, including but not limited to: name, email address and age. Ignite uses this information to authenticate Users and to send notifications to those Users relating to Ignite services.  
Ignite may also collect other profile data, including but not limited to: personal interests, personal, gender, age, education and occupation. Ignite uses this information to assist it in providing services to Users.

The Site may also log non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate User data, and browser type from Users on this site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage, and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to Users. Additionally, User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.  
User profile information, including personal pictures and/or avatars, in game video replays, competition results, as well as user names, may be used by Ignite for promotional purposes.  When Ignite may use such information for promotional purposes it will state this in the relevant Terms and Conditions of the particular service/product, such Terms and Conditions being accessible from the Site and the terms of which must be agreed to by relevant participating Users.  
Email addresses are used to send notifications related to the services/products offered by the Site. Email addresses of Users are not made available to other Users.

We may also use a User’s email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the Site or other Ignite services/products. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by following the instructions in the relevant email. 

The Site contains links to external sites. Ignite is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site, a User should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on the Site and or by Ignite directly. 

Please be aware that should the User voluntarily post/upload information for inclusion on the Site, including (but not limited to) submissions of tracks, cars, mods, skins, submissions to forums, bulletin boards, wikis, comment sections, message boards, classifieds, or any other public forum on the Site that such information can be accessed by the public and may in turn be used by those people to send the User unsolicited communications. 

The Site member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. Ignite takes precautions to ensure that member account information is kept private and Ignite uses reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and restrict access to member information solely to those employees who need access to perform their job functions (e.g., our customer service personnel and technical staff). Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. 

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Ignite will not disclose personal information to any third party, unless it believes that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process received by Ignite, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce Ignite’s Terms and Conditions or to protect its rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and Users of the Ignites services.

Ignite reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of ignite or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the section below.   
From time to time, Ignite may make changes to this Privacy Policy. If such changes are made, Ignite will post them on the Site to notify Users of the changes. Information about what data Ignite collects, how Ignite uses it, and when Ignite may disclose it, will always be available to Users.

The User is bound by any changes to this Privacy Policy when he or she uses the site after those changes have been posted.
